Indiana University Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology records, 1942-2010 C383
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology records
1942-2010
1955-2002
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University, Bloomington. Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology
C383
16.4 cubic feet 19 boxes
The Indiana University Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology was formally established in 2000 through the merging of the Department of Folklore (1978-2000) and the Ethnomusicology Institute (1980-2000) and is the parent department of the IU Folklore Institute and IU Ethnomusicology Institute. This collection contains administrative files, subject files, correspondence, files and audio recordings of the Special Projects unit, grant and budget information, and conference files produced by the department and its affiliated institutes from 1942 through 2010.
Access Restrictions
All subject files referring to individuals are restricted due to sensitive information. Additional restricted files are noted in the container list.
Advanced notice required for access to the collection.
Administrative History
Folklore as a discipline arrived at Indiana University with the hiring of Stith Thompson in 1921. Thompson served as director of the freshman English program and taught the first course in folklore at IU, The Ballad, The Folktale, and The Romance, in 1922. In 1942, Thompson established the Folklore Institute of America, a quadrennial gathering of American folklore students and scholars. Folklore was an interdepartmental program in 1949 and students could earn M.A. and Ph.D. degrees in folklore beginning in the 1949-1950 academic year. At this time, many folklore courses were taught under the auspices of the English Department and the program was housed in one room in the old main library. Richard M. Dorson was hired as a professor of history and folklore in 1957 and served as the Chairman of the Committee on Folklore. Under his leadership, the program expanded significantly in quality and quantity. The quadrennial Folklore Institutes continued through 1970, but in 1963, under the dynamic leadership of Richard Dorson, Indiana University formally established a permanent Folklore Institute as an academic unit within the College of Arts and Sciences. During the 1971-72 academic year, IU began offering a bachelor's degree in folklore.
Ethnomusicology was introduced to Indiana University in 1948 by George Herzog, who came to Bloomington from Columbia University. Herzog's first Ethnomusicology class was a two-semester Anthropology course, Folk and Primitive Music. In the 1950s when Herzog's health began to fail, George List, an Indiana PhD in Music (1954) took over many of his activities. List accepted a permanent appointment in Folklore in 1956. The Ethnomusicology Program was formally recognized as an interdepartmental program in the Folklore Department in 1980.
In 1978, the Folklore Department was established and Richard Dorson served as the first Chairman and Director. The Folklore Institute was established as a separate unit from the Folklore Department in 1978. The Institute promotes research and publication projects.
The Folklore Institute has a history of publishing prominent folklore journals. The Journal of the Folklore Institute (the Journal of Folklore Research as of 2002) includes articles of international scope and a prominent folklorist typically serves as editor. Indiana Folklore was a major regional journal from 1968-1980. Indiana Folklore and Oral History operated from 1980-1987 and was published in conjunction with the Oral History Research Center. The Special Projects unit of the Folklore Department was created in 1979 with the goal of obtaining external funding for publications, conferences, videos, research, and outreach activities. Between 1979 and 1992, Special Projects received $807,994 in external funding on 22 projects.
In January 2000, the Folklore Department merged with the Ethnomusicology Institute to become the Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology. The Department carries out the teaching mission at the undergraduate and graduate levels, and the Special Projects unit promotes and organizes a variety of research and outreach activities.
Arrangement
The Indiana University Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology records are organized into three series: Folklore Institute, Ethnomusicology Institute, and Special Projects.
Scope and Content Note
The Indiana University Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology records include administrative files, subject files, correspondence, files and audio recordings of the Special Projects unit, grant and budget information, and conference files produced by the department from 1942 through 2010. The collection is organized into three series: Folklore Institute, Ethnomusicology Institute, and Special Projects.
The Folklore Institute series is further organized into three subseries: Administrative files (1942-2007), General subject files (1965-2002), and Individual subject files (1965-2007). Administrative files contains materials pertaining to the day-to-day activities of the Folklore Institute including faculty meeting minutes, curriculum information, newsletters, teaching resources, departmental reviews, publicity materials, and histories of the department. Both subject files subseries contain correspondence, clippings, promotional materials, and other documents. Files in the General subject files subseries pertain primarily to folklore societies, publishers, and other organizations, while Individual subject files mainly contain material related to IU faculty, staff, students, visiting professors and speakers, and other members of the folklore field. Each subseries is organized alphabetically.
The Ethnomusicology Institute series (1973-2008), contains materials relating to Archives of Traditional Music grants, ethnomusicology faculty meetings, publications, brochures, correspondence, courses, student information, and faculty service. The series is organized alphabetically by folder heading.
The Special Projects (1944-2010) series contains materials from the Special Projects unit of the IU Folklore Department. The Special Projects unit of the Folklore Department was created in 1979 with the goal of obtaining external funding for publications, conferences, videos, research, and outreach activities. The Special Projects series has four subseries: General Project Files, Grant Proposals and Budget Information, Conferences and Colloquia, and Public Initiatives.
The General Project Files (1944-2010) subseries is arranged alphabetically and contains miscellaneous Special Project unit records including files related to the Folklore Archives Motif Index Computer Project, the Richard M. Dorson Award for Outstanding Papers in Folklore, the annual Ghost Walk, and Traditional Arts Indiana (TAI).
The Grants and Budget Information (1975-2005) subseries houses records of the Special Projects Unit's funded and unfunded project proposals to the National Endowment for the Humanities, the Smithsonian, and the Indiana Humanities Council. The subseries includes correspondence, budget breakdowns, departmental memos, instructions for the application process, and copies of the official proposals. Project proposals included in this subseries relate to research grants, community programming, assisting folklore repositories on campus, and funding folklore publications at IU.
The Conferences and Colloquia (1979-2017) subseries is arranged chronologically to replicate the conference-planning process and grouped together within the series. Many materials in this subseries relate to the conferences "The Kalevala, The Comparative Method and Beyond: A Symposium of American and Finnish Folklore," held in the Indiana University Memorial Union from September 25-28, 1985, and "Cultural Basics: Educating with the Grain," a cross-disciplinary conference in folklore and history-making in the classroom that took place on June 19-20, 1992.
The Public Initiatives (1967-2007) subseries contains records related to a joint residency program between Indiana University and the American Folklore Society, the annual folklore summer field school, the Tales On-Line (TOL) project, service-learning folklore courses, the Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, oral history interviews on audiocassettes and U-matics, and teaching materials for local elementary schools. The subseries is organized alphabetically.
Separated Material
A number of photographs, negatives, and slides were removed from the collection and are housed with the Archives Photograph Collection. These include individual and group photographs of department faculty and staff; images from festivals, reunions, and other events; and research and project photographs. For further information, please contact the Indiana University Archives staff.
Related Material
The Indiana University Archives holds a number of collections related to folklore at Indiana University, including faculty papers, student research and course papers, research and project records, and publications. The majority of these collections are described in Archives Online. For more information, please contact the archives staff.
Additional records such as newsletters, annual reports, bulletins, and publications may be accessed in the Archives of Institutional Memory.
Acquisition Information
Accession: 2003/055, 2007/047, 2016/085, 2018/048
Provenance
Transferred from the IU Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology in 2003, 2007, and 2016.
Appraisal
Disposed of monthly statement of accounts, removed duplicates of folklore journals, disposed of photocopied lecture materials that lacked annotations, removed IU publications, and disposed of student time sheets.
Folklore--Study and teaching (Higher)--Indiana--Bloomington--History--Sources.; Ethnomusicology--Study and teaching (Higher)--Indiana--Bloomington--History--Sources.; Indiana University, Bloomington. Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology -- Archives
- Folklore Institute, 1942-2007 (Box 1)
  - Administrative files, 1942-2007 (Box 1)
    - 60 years of Folkloristics at IU, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
    - Admission / Enrollment Statistics and M.A./ Ph.D. Committee Lists, 1948-1999 (Box 1)
    - African Studies, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Annual Fellowships Report, Folklore Institute Accounts, 1977-1984 (Box 1)
    - Articles on Folklore Institute and Faculty, 1966-1974 (Box 1)
    - Arts and Sciences Expo, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Assessment Plan, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Bloomington General Information and History, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Business, 2005-2006 (Box 14)
      Conditions Governing Access
      (RESTRICTED)
    - Career Goals, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Classroom Materials - mostly F220 Intro to American Folklore exams, 1980-1982 (Box 1)
    - Computer Purchase Information, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
    - Conference Bulletins, 1970-1973 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2007 (Box 1)
    - Curriculum Committee Folklore, 1979-1982 (Box 1)
    - Curriculum: Dual Degree SLIS, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Curriculum Information - Undergraduate, 1988-1994 (Box 1)
    - Department Assistantships, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - Departmental Brochures, 1975-1980 (Box 1)
    - Department Review, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Dissertation Defense Announcements (Box 1)
      - 1958-1969 (Box 1)
      - 1970-1979 (Box 1)
      - 1980-1989 (Box 1)
      - 1990-1999 (Box 1)
      - 2000-2010 (Box 1)
    - Dissertation Qualifying Exams, 1990-2000; (18 folders) (Box 20)
    - Draft Proposal for Core Curriculum, 1991 (Box 20)
    - Educational Opportunity Fellowship, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Faculty Business, Curriculum Changes, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1995-1997 (Box 1)
    - Faculty Summary Reports and Special Projects Unit Reports, 1992-1998 (Box 1)
    - Folklore Account Book, 1988-2006 (Box 1)
    - Folklore Committees, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Folklore Curriculum, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Folklore Flyers, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Folklore Institute (Box 1)
      - General, 1942-1995; (4 folders) (Box 1)
      - Folklore Student Association, Archives of Traditional Music Publications, 1969-1988 (Box 1)
      - Memos, 1989-2001 (Box 1)
    - Folklore Institute Report, 1984-1985; (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Folklore Shuffle (Song about Members of the Department, undated (Box 1)
    - Governance Policies and Department History, 2003-2007 (Box 14)
    - Grad House Programs and Staff, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Grants, 2005-2007 (Box 2)
    - Guide to the Dorson Memorial Library, undated (Box 2)
    - How to: Computer Applications in Ethno-Dance-Folklore, 1992; 1 floppy disc (Box 2)
    - Institute News Releases, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
    - International Programs, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Latin American Studies, 1996 (Box 2)
    - Letter from Modern Language Association re: MLA Int'l Bibl.; response from Richard M. Dorson; Draft of letter to President Ryan et al., 1981, 1992-1994 (Box 2)
    - Letters to be written for Dorson Fund, 1985 (Box 2)
    - M.A. Exam Info, 1997-1999 (Box 2)
    - Memorial Service for Richard M. Dorson, September 24, 1981; (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Minority Faculty Fellowship, 1995-2002 (Box 14)
    - Misc. Documents, Warren E. Roberts, 1943-1982 (Box 2)
    - Misc. Research Material Information, 1948-1976 (Box 2)
    - Newsletter - Summer Seminar, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Other Folklore and Ethnomusicology Programs, undated (Box 2)
    - Outlines/Lecture Notes/Guides from Folklore Institute Summer Sessions, 1942-1946 (Box 2)
    - Planning for Excellence, 1981-1986 (Box 2)
    - Ph.D. Qualifying Exams, 1989-2000 (Box 2)
    - Preparing Future Faculty (PFF), 1995 (Box 2)
    - Proposal for Undergraduate Degree in Folklore, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Quality Report, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Recommendations, 1998-2006 (Box 14)
    - Research and Development, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
    - Research Center for Languages and Semiotic Studies – (Publications), 1979 (Box 2)
    - Reunion and Tradition, 1990-1997 (Box 2)
    - The Richmond Family Trust, Appraisal of Library Collection by the Bookcellar, September 28, September 28, 1944 (Box 2)
    - Richard M. Dorson Memorial Fund, 1981-1989 (Box 2)
    - Society for Asian Folklore, 1966-1968 (Box 2)
    - Stith Thompson Biography – Sketch, undated (Box 2)
    - Strategic Directions, 1996, 2002 (Box 2)
    - Student Exit Surveys, 1996-2005 (Box 14)
    - Summer Session Budget, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Teaching Capacity Model, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Teaching Resources Center, Fall 1996 (Box 2)
    - Tenure – Official Documents Samples, 1979-1984 (Box 14)
    - To all those who plotted to surprise me [Richard M. Dorson] on 3-13-81, March 15, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Undergrad Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 2)
    - Undergraduate Major/Minor worksheets, undated (Box 2)
    - University Fund Drive - Folklore Department and Institute, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
    - Velma Carmichael, Retirement, 2007 (Box 2)
  - General subject files, 1965-2002 (Box 2)
    - American Folklore Society, 1978-1992 (Box 2)
    - American Historical Association, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Annual Review of Anthropology, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
    - Arete, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Arkansas Arts Council, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Arno Press, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
    - Boston Public Library, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
    - Dorson, Richard: Obituary and Vita, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Doubleday, 1972, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1958-1974 (Box 2)
    - Enzyklopadie des Marchens, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Fabula, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Farmshouse Films, Inc., 1981 (Box 2)
    - Fawcett, 1972-1979 (Box 2)
    - The Folklore Society - Univ. College London, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Folktales of Egypt, University of Chicago Press, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
    - Folktales of India, 1979-1983 (Box 2)
    - Folktales Told Around the World: University of Chicago Press, 1972-1981 (Box 2)
    - Gale Research Company, 1973-1982 (Box 2)
    - Greenwood, Janet, Ishi, 1976-1981 (Box 2)
    - Greenwood Press, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1973-1981 (Box 2)
    - Hackett Publishing Company, 1975, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Harvard University Press, 1974-1981 (Box 3)
    - Hicks, Gipsey, Southern Illinois University Press, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Huntington Library, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Huntington Library, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Indiana Cooperative Library Services Authority (INCOLSA), 2003 (Box 3)
    - Indiana Folklore, 1981-1983 (Box 3)
    - Indiana Humanities Council, 1984-1993 (Box 3)
    - Institute for Scientific Information, 1981 (Box 3)
    - List of Folklore and Folklore-related Journals Published in North America, undated (Box 3)
    - Mid-South Folklore, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Midwest Folklore, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Monroe County Community Access Television, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Mouton, 1973-1978 (Box 3)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities - Washington, 1977-1989 (Box 3)
    - Nepalese Folklore Society, 1986 (Box 3)
    - New York State Folklore Society, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
    - News Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
      Separated Materials
      Original photographs moved to Archives Photograph Collection
    - Oral History Assoc., 1970-1971 (Box 4)
    - Pantheon Books, 1974-1991 (Box 4)
    - Publicity: Folklore Institute, May 7, 1979 to May 6, 1980 (Box 4)
    - Reader's Digest, 1974-1977 (Box 4)
    - Reviews: Land of the Millrats, 1980-1982 (Box 4)
    - Roberts - Outdoor Museum, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Routledge and Kegan Paul, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
    - Scribners, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
    - Smithsonian, 1978-1981 (Box 4)
    - Times Literary Supplement - England, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Tuttle, Charles E., 1973-1978 (Box 4)
    - University of California Press, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1974-1982 (Box 4)
    - University of Chicago Press Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 4)
    - University of Massachusetts Press, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
    - University of Nebraska Press, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
    - University of North Carolina Press, 1973-1980 (Box 4)
    - University of Tennessee Press, 1968-1980 (Box 4)
    - University of Texas Press, 1973-1982 (Box 4)
    - University Press of Kentucky, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
    - W. W. Norton and Co., 1978 (Box 4)
  - Individual subject files, 1965-2007 (Box 14)
    Access Restrictions
    Files in this subseries are restricted. For more information, please contact Indiana University Archives staff.
    - Abrahams, Roger, 1971-1994 (Box 14)
    - Adams, Robert J., 1973-1977 (Box 14)
    - Adedji, Joel, 1978-1980 (Box 14)
    - Adeola, James, 1981-1984 (Box 14)
    - Adler, Betsy, 1979-1981 (Box 14)
    - Allen, Barbara, March 23, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Allen, Michael, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Alvey, Gerald, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Anderson, Dale, 1979-1992 (Box 14)
    - Anderson, Richard W., 1991-1995 (Box 14)
    - Annala, Ellen K., 1979 (Box 14)
    - ANSIB Associates Allan Sibul, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Imti Temsula Ao (Visiting Research Assoc.), Fulbright, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
    - Arbuckle, Gavin, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Archives of the Folklore Institute, 1973-1977 (Box 14)
    - Arnold, Gail, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Attebery, Jennifer, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Babcock, Barbara, 1977-1981 (Box 14)
    - Baker, Ronald, 1970-1980 (Box 14)
    - Bar-Itzak, Haya - Haipa University, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Barton, David, May 14, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Bascom, Williams, 1970, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Basso, Keith, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Bates, Norma L., 1978 (Box 14)
    - Batson, Trent and Pat McNees, 1978-1980 (Box 14)
    - Bauman, Richard, 1970-2007 (Box 14)
    - Bausinger, Hermann '88, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Beaman, Anne W., 1982 (Box 14)
    - Beardslee, Elaine L., April 1982 (Box 14)
    - Beck, Brenda E. F., 1979-1981 (Box 14)
    - Beezley, William, 1978-1981 (Box 14)
    - Belanus, Betty J., 1977-1990 (Box 14)
    - Bell, Michael L., July 29, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Ben-Amos, Dan, 1970-1978 (Box 14)
    - Bendix, Regina, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Benoist, Anne, June 4, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Benzoor, Nina - Curator at Haifa Museum, documents, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Bergal, Nancy Ann, October 1980 (Box 14)
    - Berlincourt,Marjoric: NEH Program Officer, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Bichi, Abdu, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Biebuyck, Brunhilde, 1979-1981 (Box 14)
    - Biebuyck, Daniel, 1971-1980 (Box 14)
    - Bienkowska, D, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Bird, Charles, 1970-1972 (Box 14)
    - Bird, Donald, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Blache, Marta, 1980-1989 (Box 14)
    - Bocock, C. W. Wanted information on ACD [Auburn, Cord, Duesenberg], 1986 (Box 14)
    - Bodnar, John, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Bond, Alec, 1978-1980 (Box 14)
    - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1971-1979 (Box 14)
    - Borland, Katherina, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Boulton, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Bradunas, Elena, 1975-1980 (Box 14)
    - Brady, Erika (National Endowment for the Arts), 1979 (Box 14)
    - Briggs, Katharine, 1970-1978 (Box 14)
    - Bronner, Simon J., 1980-1990 (Box 14)
    - Brose, David, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
    - Brown, Lynda - Auburn University at Montgomery, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Brown, Lynda - Southwestern Humor, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Brown, Mary Ellen, 1976-1981 (Box 14)
    - Bruce, Iain, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Bruner, Edward M., 1981 (Box 14)
    - Brunvand, Jan, 1970-1982 (Box 14)
    - Buchan, David, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Buculavas, Tina - Traditional Arts in the Calumet Area, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Burlakoff, Nikolai, 1979-1981 (Box 14)
    - Burns, Thomas, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Bustin, Dillon, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
    - Camp, Charles, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Carey, George, 1972-1980 (Box 14)
    - Carpenter, Inta, 1973-1998 (Box 14)
    - Carter, Gerald - Central Michigan University, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Cassell, Nancy A., 1980-1983 (Box 14)
    - Claus, Peter J., 1978-1979 (Box 14)
    - Clements, William M., 1975-1988 (Box 15)
    - Cogswell, Roby, 1979-1981 (Box 15)
    - Cohen, Ron - IU Northwest Conference - Folk Music Revival, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
    - Collins, Camilla A., 1978-1987 (Box 15)
    - Comple, Jennifer - Indiana Arts Commission, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Cotton, Donna, 1981 (Box 15)
    - Coulter, Della, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Cowley, John, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Cravens, Hamilton, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Cray, Ed, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Creighton, Helen, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Cunningham, Kathy, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Cunningham, Keith, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
    - Dance, Daryl, 1978-1981 (Box 15)
    - Danielson, Larry, 1977-1979 (Box 15)
    - Dehnert, Edmund - Evanston, Illinois, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
    - Deja, Rick, 1993 (Box 15)
    - Dorson, Gloria, 1981-1983 (Box 15)
    - Dow, James R. - MLA [Modern Language Association] databank, 1987-1989 (Box 15)
    - Dundes, Alan, 1970-2002 (Box 15)
    - Eberhard, Wolfram, 1970-1980 (Box 15)
    - Eckley, Grace, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
    - Eder, Matthias - CV, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - El-Shamy, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
    - El-Naggar, Mohammed Ragab, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Ellis, Bill, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Fanelli, Robert N., 1980 (Box 15)
    - Feintuch, Burt, 1979-1985 (Box 15)
    - Fernandez, Carlos - MA Proposal, 1990-1992 (Box 15)
    - Ferris, William, 1973-1999 (Box 15)
    - Fine, Gary, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
    - Fish, Lydia, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Fitchen, Allen N. University of Chicago Press, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
    - Fleischhauer, Carl, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Floyd, Ann J. American Anthropological Assoc., 1988 (Box 15)
    - Folklorists Addresses, undated (Box 15)
    - Fox, William S. - Skidmore College, Accepted, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Fry, Gladys-Marie, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Garcia, Peter, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
    - George, Phil, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
    - Georges, Robert A., 1970-1980 (Box 15)
    - Glassie, Henry, 1977-1985 (Box 15)
    - Glimm, James York Mansfield State College, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Goldstein, Kenneth S., 1970-1981 (Box 15)
    - Gooding, Erik, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Goodwin, Joseph Paul, 1981-1986 (Box 15)
    - Goswami, Praphulladata, 1971-1980 (Box 15)
    - Green, Archie, 1973-1999 (Box 15)
    - Green, Rayna, 1971-1974 (Box 15)
    - Grider, Sylvia, 1983 (Box 15)